Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series X: Audio-Visual Material, 1957-2009
  - Subseries X:C: Audio Reel-to-Reel, 1957-1975
    - National Archives and Record Service: Recording of the Demonstration and Shooting at Kent State by Steve Titchenal (played at Public Hearings in Kent, Ohio, Aug 19 and 21, 1970), May 4, 1970 (Box 79, Reel 285)
    - National Archives and Record Service: Interviews on the Street in Kent City (May 7, 1970) / KNT (ABC) Radio Pickup of Richard Nixon Press Conference on the Cambodia Invasion and Kent State (May 8, 1970), May 7, 1970/May 8, 1970 (Box 79, Reel 286)
    - WBUR: Is Justice Done? - Bruce Prager, Law and Justice in America (Final Project for PO 506 Boston, MA), Dec 3, 1973 (Box 79, Reel 287)
    - Ralph Nader: Speech, Oct 2, 1974 (Box 79, Reel 288)
    - National Public Radio: Henry Kissinger - Statement on Vietnam Tape 1, Jan 2, 1975 (Box 79, Reel 289)
    - National Public Radio: Henry Kissinger - Statement on Vietnam Tape 2, Jan 2, 1975 (Box 79, Reel 290)
    - Charlie Crafts: Prisons, Justice and the Role of Students (guest lecturer in Howard Zinn's Class), Mid- 1970s (Box 79, Reel 291)
    - Bob Zellner and Unidentified Activist: Discussion on SNCC (With Howard Zinn), undated (Box 79, Reel 292)
    - Christmas Music and Spoken Word: Includes Signed Letter (Recorded at 1 7/8 Speed), undated (Box 79, Reel 293)
    - Unidentified Comedy Show on Sound Effects, undated (Box 79, Reel 294)
    - Unidentified Lecture on the Chinese Language, undated (Box 79, Reel 295)
    - Unidentified Student Panel on Communes in China (includes Ping-chia Kuo, Howard Zinn, [William] Worthy, [Richard] Walker, and Cole), undated (Box 79, Reel 296)
    - V. Watson: China's Policy Towards Asia (guest lecturer in Howard Zinn's Class), undated (Box 79, Reel 297)
    - Various: Includes Chinese Language Interviews with Owen Lattimore, Derk Bodde, and Allen Watts; Howard Zinn on Geopolitics in China and Taoism; Oriental Music (Kagan), undated (Box 79, Reel 298)
  - Subseries X:D: Video DVDs, 1991-2009
    - "Howard Zinn - 1492-1992: Reclaiming the People's History" Presented by KBOO FM and MRG, at Portland State University (The Flying Focus Video Collective) Disk 1 of 2, Oct 10, 1991 (Box 80, Disk 299)
    - "Howard Zinn - 1492-1992: Reclaiming the People's History" Presented by KBOO FM and MRG, at Portland State University (The Flying Focus Video Collective) Disk 2 of 2, Oct 10, 1991 (Box 80, Disk 300)
    - Howard Zinn at U.C. Santa Cruz Disk 1 of 2, Jan 28, 1992 (Box 80, Disk 301)
    - Howard Zinn at U.C. Santa Cruz Disk 2 of 2, Jan 28, 1992 (Box 80, Disk 302)
    - Howard Zinn "The Gulf War in Moral and Historical Perspective" at Boston College Disk 1 of 2, Feb 5, 1992 (Box 80, Disk 303)
    - Howard Zinn "The Gulf War in Moral and Historical Perspective" at Boston College Disk 2 of 2, Feb 5, 1992 (Box 80, Disk 304)
    - Howard Zinn "The Uses of History" at the University of Minnesota, Duluth Disk 1 of 2, Nov 7, 1996 (Box 80, Disk 305)
    - Howard Zinn "The Uses of History" at the University of Minnesota, Duluth Disk 2 of 2, Nov 7, 1996 (Box 80, Disk 306)
    - Howard Zinn at Madison Disk 1 of 2, Nov 1997 (Box 80, Disk 307)
    - Howard Zinn at Madison Disk 2 of 2, Nov 1997 (Box 80, Disk 308)
    - Howard Zinn "Civil Rights and Economic Justice, Race and Class in America" at Bates College, Lewiston, Maine, May 7, 1998 (Box 80, Disk 309)
    - Howard Zinn A People's History of the United States at the Ask with Education Forum, Harvard Graduate School of Education Disk 1 of 2, Feb 17, 1999 (Box 80, Disk 310)
    - Howard Zinn A People's History of the United States at the Ask with Education Forum, Harvard Graduate School of Education Disk 2 of 2, Feb 17, 1999 (Box 80, Disk 311)
    - Howard Zinn A People's History of the United States Booknotes (CSPAN), Jan 26, 2000 (Box 80, Disk 312)
    - Howard Zinn at Wisconsin Union Theater Disk 1 of 2, Apr 18, 2000 (Box 80, Disk 313)
    - Howard Zinn at Wisconsin Union Theater Disk 2 of 2, Apr 18, 2000 (Box 80, Disk 314)
    - Howard Zinn: Slideshow DVD, 2002-2008 (Box 80, Disk 315)
    - Howard Zinn on Book TV (CSPAN) Disk 1 of 3, Sep 1, 2002 (Box 80, Disk 316)
    - Howard Zinn on Book TV (CSPAN) Disk 2 of 3, Sep 1, 2002 (Box 80, Disk 317)
    - Howard Zinn on Book TV (CSPAN) Disk 3 of 3, Sep 1, 2002 (Box 80, Disk 318)
    - "Now" with Bill Moyers: Show # 202 (WNET, New York), Jan 10, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 319)
    - Howard Zinn at the New School University with Joe Friendly for NYC Indy Media, Feb 11, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 320)
    - Howard Zinn at the New School University with Joe Friendly for NYC Indy Media (DV Cassette 1 of 2), Feb 11, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 321)
    - Howard Zinn at the New School University with Joe Friendly for NYC Indy Media (DV Cassette 2 of 2), Feb 11, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 322)
    - Arundhati Roy with Howard Zinn: "Come September" (Santa Fe), May 13, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 323)
    - A Conversation: Woody Harrelson and Howard Zinn (Freespeech TV), Oct 4, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 324)
    - Howard Zinn "Speaking Truth to Empire: End the Occupation of Iraq" Teach-In at Harvard University / Noam Chomsky "End the Occupation of Palestine" at Harvard University, Dec 4, 2003/Dec 10, 2003 (Box 80, Disk 325)
    - Marx in Soho with Danny Bryck, Directed by Bob Brick at the PUPA Studio Theater, Mar 2005 (Box 80, Disk 326)
    - "Rebel Voices" (First Public Reading) Adapted from Voices of A People's History of the United States, Jul 27, 2005 (Box 80, Disk 327)
    - "Readings from Voices of A People's History of the United States" at the George and Sakye Aratani Japan America Theatre, Los Angeles, CA, Oct 5, 2005 (Box 80, Disk 328)
    - Ward Churchill "Kill the Indian, Save the Man; The Genocidal Impact of the American Indian Residential Schools" at the Tattered Cover Bookstore, Denver CO, Nov 11, 2005 (Box 80, Disk 329)
    - Kenwood Dennard and Howard Zinn at Berklee College of Music, Mar 31, 2006 (Box 80, Disk 330)
    - Howard Zinn: "Bringing Democracy Alive" Boston University (first of endowed Howard Zinn Lecture Series), Nov 2, 2006 (Box 80, Disk 331)
    - Howard Zinn: "Bringing Democracy Alive" Boston University (first of endowed Howard Zinn Lecture Series), Nov 2, 2006 (Box 80, Disk 331 dup)
    - "Deconstructing Occupation" Howard Zinn, Scott Ritter and a Proposal to Create an Israeli-Palestinian Confederation (3 Events: Chapman University, Orange, CA/Dutton's Books, Brentwood CA/Beverly Hills, CA Public Library), Nov 2, 2006/Nov 8, 2006/Nov 12, 2006 (Box 80, Disk 332)
    - Howard Zinn Interview by Julian Schlossberg, [Nov 13, 2006] (Box 80, Disk 333)
    - Howard Zinn Interview by Julian Schlossberg, [Nov 13, 2006] (Box 80, Disk 333 dup)
    - "A Poetic tribute to Daniel Berrigan" at the Friends Meeting House in Cambridge, MA (Arrowsmith Books / Radio Free Maine), Dec 2, 2006 (Box 80, Disk 334)
    - Howard Zinn Appears in Sacco and Vanzetti by Willow Pond Films, 2006 (Box 80, Disk 335)
    - Howard Zinn: "The War on Terrorism and the Uses of History" (Havens Center, Orpheum Theatre Madison, WI), 2006 (Box 80, Disk 336)
    - Howard Zinn: "The War on Terrorism and the Uses of History" (Havens Center, Orpheum Theatre Madison, WI), 2006 (Box 80, Disk 336 dup)
    - Nanking (documentary film written by Elisabeth Bentley), Jan 16, 2007 (Box 80, Disk 337)
    - Howard Zinn: Acceptance Speech, Lifetime Achievement Award from WPFW (Pacifica DC), Dec 15, 2007 (Box 80, Disk 338)
    - "The People Speak" Howard Zinn and Others (WHAT), 2007 (Box 80, Disk 339)
    - Profit Motive and the Whispering Wind A Film by John Gianvito, 2007 (Box 80, Disk 340)
    - Marx in Soho: Norfolk, VA, Jan 2008 (Box 80, Disk 341)
    - Howard Zinn at Farmingham High School, Feb 14, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 342)
    - The Hour w/George Stroumboulopoulos, Canada's Late Night Talk Show: Howard Zinn Appearance, Sep 25, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 343)
    - Howard Zinn "The Meaning of Sacco and Vanzetti" also Robert D'Attilio narrates Sacco and Vanzetti Funeral Procession and David Rothauser reads letters of Sacco and Vanzetti at the Dante Alighieri Society Italian Cultural Center, Cambridge, MA, Nov 7, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 344)
    - Howard Zinn "War and Social Justice" at Binghamton University, Nov 8, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 345)
    - Noam Chomsky "What's Next, on Elections, the Economy and the Global Challenges of Our Time" at the Arlington Street Church, Boston MA, Nov 19, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 346)
    - Howard Zinn: Oral History Interview (Brooklyn Navy Yard), Dec 8, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 347)
    - Howard Zinn: Oral History Interview (Brooklyn Navy Yard), Dec 8, 2008 (Box 80, Disk 347 dup)
    - Bill Moyers Journal: "Obama's Wars" with Marilyn Young and Pierre Sprey, Jan 30, 2009 (Box 80, Disk 348)
    - Howard Zinn at Progressive Magazine's 100th Anniversary (Madison, WI), May 17, 2009 (Box 80, Disk 349)
    - Howard Zinn at Progressive Magazine's 100th Anniversary (Madison, WI), May 17, 2009 (Box 80, Disk 349 dup)
    - "The Promise of Change: Vision and Reality in Obama's Presidency" Boston University Howard Zinn Lecture Series: Panel includes Howard Zinn, Mary Gordon, James Carroll, and Ellen Goodman, Oct 22, 2009 (Box 80, Disk 350)
    - Bill Moyers Journal: Show # 1332 - with Jane Goodall, Nov 27, 2009 (Box 80, Disk 351)
    - Oliver Stone: "A Bill Moyers Essay: War Powers" (Show # 1333), Dec 4, 2009 (Box 80, Disk 352)
    - Cambridge Public Library Author Series: Howard Zinn, undated (Box 80, Disk 353)
    - Marx in Soho: Cuban Film (in Spanish), undated (Box 80, Disk 354)
    - Marx in Soho: Jerry Levy, undated (Box 80, Disk 355)
    - Marx in Soho: Teaching Support DVD with clips from the production and study questions (includes an interview with Robert Weick), undated (Box 80, Disk 356)
  - Subseries X:E: Video VHS, 1986-2007
    - Howard Zinn and Dan Berrigan: Prisoner Release - NBC Footage, [1968] (Box 81, Video 357)
    - Conference on Covert Action (Kennedy Library), Apr 22, 1986 (Box 81, Video 358)
    - Howard Zinn at East Central University (Ada, OK), Oct 9, 1990 (Box 81, Video 359)
    - Howard Zinn Interview (Dallas, TX), Oct 1990 (Box 81, Video 360)
    - Howard Zinn on the Today Show, Dec 18, 1990 (Box 81, Video 361)
    - Gulf War Teach-In at Bentley College, Jan 24, 1991 (Box 81, Video 362)
    - Howard Zinn at UMass / Noam Chomsky "Talk Live" TV Show / Bill Moyers "After the War", Mar 28, 1991/May 29, 1991/undated (Box 81, Video 363)
    - Howard Zinn: "1492-1992 - What is There to Celebrate?", Apr 12, 1991 (Box 81, Video 364)
    - Howard Zinn at San Diego State University / Bo Gritz, John Stockwell, and Kwame Ture (Stokely Carmichael) Speaking at SDSU, Apr 17, 1991 / undated (Box 81, Video 365)
    - Howard Zinn Interview (Boston, MA), Jul 1991 (Box 81, Video 366)
    - Howard Zinn on "The Opinion Page: The Gulf War", Sep 6, 1991 (Box 81, Video 367)
    - Howard Zinn: "1492-1992: Reclaiming the People's History", Oct 10, 1991 (Box 81, Video 368)
    - Boston Common: "JFK / Police Commission" (Howard Zinn on Panel), Jan 12, 1992 (Box 81, Video 369)
    - Howard Zinn at U.C. Santa Cruz, Jan 28, 1992 (Box 81, Video 370)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Gulf War in Moral and Historical Perspective" (Boston College), Feb 5, 1992 (Box 81, Video 371)
    - Howard Zinn: Ames Interview, 1992 (Box 81, Video 372)
    - Howard Zinn: "Democracy and Disobedience" (CCSU, Hartford CT), Apr 27, 1993 (Box 81, Video 373)
    - "Legacy": Chief Crazy Horse / Jeff Baker, Nov 11, 1993 (Box 81, Video 374)
    - Howard Zinn: "Boston Common", Jan 22, 1995 (Box 81, Video 375)
    - Howard Zinn: "Government for the People?" The Somerville Producers Group Presents Dead Air Live, Jul 18, 1995 (Box 81, Video 376)
    - Howard Zinn: "Building Community in a Class Society" Mankato State University (Mankato, MN), Nov 14, 1995 (Box 81, Video 377)
    - Howard Zinn: Informal Brown Bag Lunch, Nov 16, 1995 (Box 81, Video 378)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview at Santa Rosa, CA, Apr 22, 1996 (Box 81, Video 379)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Possibility of Hope" Resource Center for Nonviolence Santa Cruz, CA, Oct 25, 1996 (Box 81, Video 380)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Uses of History" (University of Minnesota, Duluth), Nov 7, 1996 (Box 81, Video 381)
    - Malden Public Radio: MPR #123, Jan 6, 1997 (Box 81, Video 382)
    - Howard Zinn at KVCC, Apr 16, 1997 (Box 81, Video 383)
    - Howard Zinn at KVCC, Apr 16, 1997 (Box 81, Video 383 dup)
    - Howard Zinn at Santa Cruz High School, Nov 14, 1997 (Box 81, Video 384)
    - Howard Zinn at Cody's, Nov 14, 1997 (Box 81, Video 385)
    - Howard Zinn: River College, Nov 24, 1997 (Box 82, Video 386)
    - Howard Zinn Interview at Community Television Santa Cruz, CA, Nov 1997 (Box 82, Video 387)
    - Howard Zinn: Madison, WI, Nov 1997 (Box 82, Video 388)
    - Howard Zinn: Haverhill High School, Apr 8, 1998 (Box 82, Video 389)
    - Howard Zinn: "An Economic Bill of Rights" (United Food and Commercial Workers, Union Hall Denver, CO), Oct 5, 1998 (Box 82, Video 390)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel (Berkeley), 1998 (Box 82, Video 391)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel (Berkeley), 1998 (Box 82, Video 391 dup)
    - Marx in Soho, 1998 (Box 82, Video 392)
    - Howard Zinn A People's History of the United States Harvard Graduate School of Education, Harvard Education Forum, Feb 17, 1999 (Box 82, Video 393)
    - Howard Zinn at NERC Boston, Mar 1999 (Box 82, Video 394)
    - Howard Zinn: "Kosovo" MSNBC, Apr 3, 1999 (Box 82, Video 395)
    - "An Evening with Howard Zinn and Clayborne Carson" A Benefit for Speak Out and KPFA at King Middle School (Berkeley CA), May 7, 1999 (Box 82, Video 396)
    - Howard Zinn Who?: Liberty Hill Foundation, Jun 24, 1999 (Box 82, Video 397)
    - Howard Zinn: Booknotes CSPAN, Jan 26, 2000 (Box 82, Video 398)
    - "People's History: An Evening with Howard Zinn and Ben Affleck", Mar 21, 2000 (Box 82, Video 399)
    - Howard Zinn: DLS Wisconsin Union Theater, Apr 18, 2000 (Box 82, Video 400)
    - Howard Zinn: "The People's History of U.S. Relations with Cuba" ("Let Cuba Live" Fundraiser for the 11th - Pastors for Peace US/Cuba Friendship Caravan), Oct 4, 2000 (Box 82, Video 401)
    - "War": MSNBC, Sep 19, 2001 (Box 82, Video 402)
    - "Celebrating Richard A. Cloward's Life and Work", Sep 20, 2001 (Box 82, Video 403)
    - Howard Zinn on the Current Crisis (UVM), Oct 21, 2001 (Box 82, Video 404)
    - Democracy Now: Howard Zinn Speech (Burlington, VT), Oct 2001 (Box 82, Video 405)
    - An Evening with Howard Zinn: "People Making History" (Santa Cruz, CA), Nov 2001 (Box 82, Video 406)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's Historian (CWRU, Cleveland, OH), 2001 (Box 82, Video 407)
    - Howard Zinn: Cambridge, Jan 29, 2002 (Box 82, Video 408)
    - Howard Zinn: Alliance for Democracy (Cambridge, MA), Feb 10, 2002 (Box 82, Video 409)
    - Howard Zinn: "U.S. Foreign Policy, Terrorism and Global Security" (Cambridge, MA), Feb 10, 2002 (Box 82, Video 410)
    - Howard Zinn: "Bringing Democracy Alive" (Shoreline Community College, Seattle, WA), Apr 10, 2002 (Box 82, Video 411)
    - Howard Zinn with Students of Boston Evening Academy, Jun 2002 (Box 82, Video 412)
    - Howard Zinn on CSPAN, Sep 1, 2002 (Box 82, Video 413)
    - Howard Zinn: "You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train" - Rough Cut, Sep 2002 (Box 82, Video 414)
    - "Not in Our Name: An Evening of Conscience": Cooper Union (Howard Zinn Appearance), Oct 3, 2002 (Box 83, Video 415)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Legacy of the Civil Rights Movement in the Age of Terrorism" at the Bates College Chapel in Lewiston, ME, Oct 14, 2002 (Box 83, Video 416)
    - Howard Zinn: "Terrorism and War" (Brown University, Providence, RI), Nov 14, 2002 (Box 83, Video 417)
    - Now w/ Bill Moyers: Episode 202 (Howard Zinn appearance), Jan 10, 2003 (Box 83, Video 418)
    - Now w/ Bill Moyers: Episode 202 (Howard Zinn appearance), Jan 10, 2003 (Box 83, Video 418 dup)
    - Howard Zinn: "Tunnel Vision vs. History" at the New School University NYC; Noam Chomsky / "Paths to Peace in the Middle East" at the University of Pennsylvania, Feb 11, 2003/Oct 4, 2002 (Box 83, Video 419)
    - Howard Zinn: "Tunnel Vision vs. History" at the New School University NYC, Speech by John Schuchardt on behalf of Philip Berrigan (also includes interview with Philip Berrigan from Feb 1997), Feb 11, 2003 (Box 83, Video 420)
    - Howard Zinn at New School University, Feb 11, 2003 (Box 83, Video 421)
    - Howard Zinn at New School University, Feb 11, 2003 (Box 83, Video 421 dup)
    - Howard Zinn at New School University (Corrected Sync), Feb 11, 2003 (Box 83, Video 422)
    - Howard Zinn at New School University (Corrected Sync), Feb 11, 2003 (Box 83, Video 422 dup)
    - "Dialogue: Why War?" with Richard Perle and Jessica Tuchman Matthew and Gwen Ifil on the News Hour with Jim Lehrer, Feb 12, 2003 (Box 83, Video 423)
    - Howard Zinn and Amy Goodman, Feb 19, 2003 (Box 83, Video 424)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States - 92nd Street Y (Aired on Democracy Now Apr 30 and May 1, 2003), Feb [23] 2003 (Box 83, Video 425)
    - The News Hour Live Shot: Jim Lehrer, Howard Zinn, Robert Dallek, Walter Russel Mead and Diane Kunz, Mar 17, 2003 (Box 83, Video 426)
    - Howard Zinn on MSNBC, Jul 13, 2003 (Box 83, Video 427)
    - Howard Zinn and Woody Harrelson on FSTV, Oct 4, 2003 (Box 83, Video 428)
    - Howard Zinn: Atlanta Book Club, Oct 22, 2003 (Box 83, Video 429)
    - Howard Zinn Talks About his Book You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (Miami Book Fair International, CSPAN), Nov 8, 2003 (Box 83, Video 430)
    - Howard Zinn: "Books of Our Time" at the Massachusetts School of Law, Nov 11, 2003 (Box 83, Video 431)
    - Tribute to a Generation: National World War II Reunion - Wartime Stories Stage, WWII Vets as Historians (Howard Zinn, participant), May 27, 2004 (Box 83, Video 432)
    - Howard Zinn and Daniel Ellsberg: Veterans Address the Nation, Jul 23, 2004 (Box 83, Video 433)
    - Howard Zinn on the Daily Show, Jan 6, 2005 (Box 83, Video 434)
    - Howard Zinn on CSPAN, Jan 14, 2005 (Box 83, Video 435)
    - Convocation: "History that Embraces Humanity" (Howard Zinn, speaker), Apr 5, 2006 (Box 83, Video 436)
    - Howard Zinn and James Carroll: "Understanding Our World", Jun 26, 2006 (Box 83, Video 437)
    - Howard Zinn at Brandeis, Jan 2007 (Box 83, Video 438)
    - Howard Zinn on Chet Curtis Report, Feb 16, 2007 (Box 83, Video 439)
    - Brandeis: The Last Teach-In, undated (Box 83, Video 440)
    - Chomsky on Bill Moyers / Zinn, Moynihan on JFK, undated (Box 83, Video 441)
    - Emma: Tokyo I, undated (Box 84, Video 442)
    - Emma: Tokyo II, undated (Box 84, Video 443)
    - Howard Zinn: Author Series at Cambridge Public Library, undated (Box 84, Video 444)
    - Howard Zinn at Barnes and Noble, undated (Box 84, Video 445)
    - Howard Zinn: "The First Amendment: A Historical Perspective", undated (Box 84, Video 446)
    - Howard Zinn: "On a Moving Train" (lecture plus Q and A session), undated (Box 84, Video 447)
    - Howard Zinn Talk: Teachers, undated (Box 84, Video 448)
    - Howard Zinn on War, undated (Box 84, Video 449)
    - Marx in Soho (Cuba), undated (Box 84, Video 450)
    - Marx in Soho (Midwest), undated (Box 84, Video 451)
    - Marx in Soho: Performed by Normal Marshall, undated (Box 84, Video 452)
    - "Other Points of View": Interview with Howard Zinn, undated (Box 84, Video 453)
    - "The Panama Deception", undated (Box 84, Video 454)
    - "The Power of People's History": SCL, undated (Box 84, Video 455)
    - Royan: Footage for Dennis Mueller, undated (Box 84, Video 456)
    - The Trials of the AVCO Plowshares: Testimony, undated (Box 84, Video 457)
    - You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train: Rough Cut, undated (Box 84, Video 458)
    - You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train: 10 Minute Trailer, undated (Box 84, Video 459)
  - Subseries X:F: Video Other Formats, 1975, undated
    - Sony 1/2" Video Tape: "Cynthia Tape 1", Apr 1, 1975 (Box 84, Cassette 460)
    - Sony 1/2" Video Tape: "David Tape 1", Sep 30 (Box 84, Cassette 461)
    - Sony 1/2" Video Tape: "Linda Tape 1", Oct 1 (Box 84, Cassette 462)
    - Sony 1/2" Video Tape: "Mike Tape 2", Oct 1 (Box 84, Cassette 463)
    - Sony 1/2" Video Tape: [Shechter], undated (Box 84, Cassette 464)
    - U-Matic Video Cassette: "Student Project, MA Victims of Crime" (includes note from Maribeth Cox), undated (Box 84, Cassette 465)
    - U-Matic Video Cassette: "High School Kids on the Draft", undated (Box 84, Cassette 466)